RG 062:043, Town of East Hartford
Connecticut State Library
- Series 9. Financial Records, 1837-1946
  - Payroll books (Box 65)
    - 1933-1937, 1 volume (Box 65)
  - Payroll, Police Dept., 1930 February - 1931 August (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Personal payroll cards, FY 1944-1945; 1 post binder (Box 66)
  - Receipts and disbursements, 1926-1932; 1 volume (Box Item 75)
  - Receipts and expenditures, 1837-1889; 1 volume (Box 66)
  - Selectmen's orders
    - 1896-1909, 1 volume (Box Item 76)
    - 1909-1917, 1 volume (Box Item 77)
  - Treasurer's payments
    - Treasurer's payments, 1927-1929; 1 post binder (Box Item 78)
    - Treasurer's payments on town orders, 1924-1929; 1 post binder (Box Item 79)
    - Treasurer's payments, 1931-1941; 1 post binder (Box Item 80)
    - Treasurer's payments, 1941-1942; 1 post binder (Box Item 81)
- Series 10. Boards, Commissions, and Committees Records, 1929-1977
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission
    - Appointments, 1974-1975 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1977, undated (Box 82, Folder 2-10)
    - Events (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Lists, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Forms, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - These States, April 16, 1975, 1974-1976 (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - Colonial Dinner, October 19, 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder 14-15)
      - Boy Scout Encampment, May 21,22,23, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - House and Garden Tour, May 22, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 17)
      - Open House at the Town Hall, May 27, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 18)
      - Open House Youth Day and Spelling Bee, May 27, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 19)
      - Rochambeau March, June 23, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 20-21)
      - 20th Century Pilgrims, June 25, 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder 22)
      - Canoe Trek, June 27, 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder 23)
      - Wickham Park Fireworks, July 4, 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder 24)
      - Bicentennial Ball, October 2, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 25)
      - Bicentennial Epilogue, October 21, 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 82, Folder 26)
      - Miscellaneous, 1975-1976, undated (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Finances (Box 82, Folder 28)
      - Bills and receipts, 1976-1977 (Box 82, Folder 28)
      - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder 29)
      - Grant applications, 1974-1975 (Box 82, Folder 30)
      - Grant reports, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder 31)
      - Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 82, Folder 32)
    - Invitations, 1975, undated (Box 82, Folder 33)
    - Meeting notices, agendas and minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 82, Folder 34)
    - Membership lists, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973, undated (Box 82, Folder 36)
    - News clippings, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 37)
    - Press releases, 1974-1976 (Box 82, Folder 38)
    - Projects (Box 82, Folder 39)
      - Forms, undated (Box 82, Folder 39)
      - Charter Oak seedling, 1976-1977 (Box 82, Folder 40)
      - East Hartford flag proposals, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 41)
      - Historical markers, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 42)
      - Identification signs, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 43)
      - Medallions, 1976-1977 (Box 82, Folder 44)
      - Pitkin House, 1975-1977 (Box 82, Folder 45)
      - Promotional items, undated (Box 82, Folder 46)
      - Time capsule, 1976-1977 (Box 82, Folder 47)
    - Publications (Box 82, Folder 49)
      - Bicentennial Cities, 1974-1976 (Box 82, Folder 48)
      - Bicentennial Gazette, 1971-1977 (Box 82, Folder 49-50)
      - Bicentennial Times, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder 51-52)
      - East Hartford brochure, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 53)
      - Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 82, Folder 54-55)
    - Schools, 1974-1976 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Solicitations, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Town Council, 1974-1975 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Memorabilia (Box 83)
      - Rochambeau March photographs, 1976 June 23; 29 prints, b&w, 8 x 10 in. (Box 83, Folder 4)
        Photographs are numbered on the back from 1 to 40. Not all numbers are present. There are 2 unnumbered photographs.
      - "Goodwin One-Room Schoolhouse, c. 1821", undated; pen & ink drawing, image size 4.5 x 6 in. (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Negatives, 2 envelopes (Box 83)
      - Bicentennial Commission of East Hartford letterhead and envelopes (Box 83)
      - Placque presented to the Bicentennial Commission from the Spirit of '76 Club (Box 83)
      - Guest book from the Colonial Dinner, 1975 October 19 (Box 83)
      - Rochambeau Day in East Hartford, 1976 June 23; 1 audio cassette (Box 83)
      - Connecticut Bicentennial flag (Box 83)
        Accompanied by letter from George W. Cyr, Program Coordinator, American Bicentennial Commission of Connecticut to Bicentennial Chairperson, April 9, 1976.
        Flags were sent to all 169 Connecticut towns.
  - Claims Committee
    - Minutes, 1931-1937; 1 volume (Box 86)
  - Finance, Board of
    - Minutes (Box 84)
      - 1929 October 21-1939 May 22, 1 volume (Box 84)
      - 1943 October 22 - 1945 September 24, 1 volume (Box 84)
      - 1945 October 10 - 1947 September 29, 1 volume (Box 84)
      - 1947 July 15 - 1948 August 30, 1 volume (Box 84)
      - 1948 March 1 - 1949 October 10, 1 volume (Box 84)
      - 1949 October 1 - 1950 September 30, 1 volume (Box 85)
      - 1950 October 1 - 1951 September 30, 1 volume (Box 85)
      - 1951 October 1 - 1952 September 30, 1 volume (Box 85)
      - 1953 October 1 - 1954 September 30, 1 volume (Box 85)
      - 1954 October 1 - 1955 September 30, 1 volume (Box 85)
      - 1955 October 1 - 1956 September 30, 1 volume (Box 85)
      - 1956 October 1 - 1957 September 30, 1 volume (Box 85)
      - 1961 October 13 - 1964 December 14, 1 volume, photocopy (Box 85)
      - 1964 October 14 - 1967 September 6, 1 volume, photocopy (Box 85)
  - Hockanum Cemetery Committee
    - Minutes, 1933-1948; 1 volume + loose papers (Box 86)
  - Insurance Committee (Box 86)
    - Minutes, 1964 February 3 - 1972 November 28; 1 volume, photocopy (Box 86)
  - Park Board (Box 86)
    - Minutes (Box 86)
      - 1945 October 24 - 1952 December 2, 1 volume, photocopy (Box 86)
      - 1953 January 1 - 1962 December 4, 1 volume, photocopy (Box 86)
      - 1963 January 8 - 1968 February 27, 1 volume, photocopy (Box 86)
  - Police Commissioners, Board of (Box 86)
    - Minutes (Box 86)
      - 1929 October 24 - 1945 March 14, 1 volume, photocopy (Box 86)
      - 1965 April 11 - 1969 November 18, 1 volume, photocopy (Box 86)
  - Welfare Commissioners, Board of (Box 86)
    - Minutes (Box 86)
      - 1955 March 8 - 1958 May 13, 1 volume, photocopy (Box 86)
      - 1958 May 13 - 1960 December 31, 1 volume, photocopy (Box 86)
      - 1965 February 9 - 1965 March 31, 1 volume, photocopy (Box 86)
- Series 11. District Records, 1890-1932
  - East Hartford Fire District
    - Administrative files, 1900-1932
      - Abatements, 1912-1928 (Box 87, Folder 1-2)
      - Annual report, 1923 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Ash collection, 1925 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Attachments, 1914-1915,1923,1928 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Auditors, 1928 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Bids, 1912,1929, undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Bonds, 1912-1928 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Budget, 1923-1926 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - Building, plumbing and electrical reports, 1928-1930 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - By-laws, 1921-1930, undated (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - Catch basins, 1914 (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - Caucus, Republican, 1928 (Box 87, Folder 13)
      - Center Hose Company, 1903, 1913-1916 (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - Certificates, Electrical and plumbing, 1924, undated (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - Chamber of Commerce, 1924-1929 (Box 87, Folder 16)
      - Charter and amendments, 1909, 1921, undated (Box 87, Folder 17)
      - Claims, 1913, 1922-1929 (Box 87, Folder 18)
      - Clean-up week report, 1919 (Box 87, Folder 19)
      - Compensation insurance, 1925, undated (Box 87, Folder 20)
      - Connecticut Company, 1910-1916 (Box 87, Folder 21)
      - Connecticut Company, 1917-1920 (Box 87, Folder 22)
      - Connecticut Company, 1921-1924 (Box 87, Folder 23)
      - Connecticut Company, 1925-1929 (Box 87, Folder 24)
      - Connecticut River Bridge and Highway District, 1913-1923, undated (Box 87, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence (Box 87, Folder 26)
        - A, 1911-1920 (Box 87, Folder 26)
        - B, 1902-1930 (Box 87, Folder 27)
        - C, 1911-1929 (Box 87, Folder 28)
        - D, 1911-1932 (Box 87, Folder 29)
        - E, 1913-1929 (Box 87, Folder 30)
        - F, 1912-1931 (Box 87, Folder 31)
        - G, 1912-1929 (Box 87, Folder 32)
        - H, 1912-1930 (Box 87, Folder 33)
        - I, 1925-1929 (Box 87, Folder 34)
        - J, 1912-1929 (Box 87, Folder 35)
        - K, 1918-1929 (Box 87, Folder 36)
        - L, 1911-1930 (Box 87, Folder 37)
        - M, 1912-1930 (Box 87, Folder 38)
        - N, 1921-1929 (Box 87, Folder 39)
        - O, 1911-1929 (Box 87, Folder 40)
        - P, 1912-1930 (Box 87, Folder 41)
        - R, 1911-1929 (Box 87, Folder 42)
        - S, 1912-1931 (Box 87, Folder 43)
        - T, 1911-1931 (Box 87, Folder 44)
        - Y, 1914-1919 (Box 87, Folder 45)
      - Counsel: Percy S. Bryant, 1911-1929, undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Crosswalks, 1910 (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - Elections, 1907-1915, undated (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - Filing report, 1913 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Financial papers, 1923-1931 (Box 88, Folder 5-9)
      - Fire alarm, 1918 (Box 88, Folder 10)
      - Fire Department, 1912, 1921-1934, undated (Box 88, Folder 11)
      - Fireworks, Applications for permits and Bonds of Indemnity, 1925-1928 (Box 88, Folder 12)
      - First selectman, 1912-1925 (Box 88, Folder 13)
      - Garbage, 1915-1929 (Box 88, Folder 14)
      - Glastonbury Fire District, 1916, 1917, 1929 (Box 88, Folder 15)
      - Hartford City Gas Light Company, 1913-1925 (Box 88, Folder 16)
      - Hartford Electric Light Company, 1909-1929 (Box 88, Folder 17-18)
      - Hartford Fire Department, 1910, 1915-1917, 1921 (Box 88, Folder 19)
      - Health officer, 1912-1927 (Box 88, Folder 20)
      - Hockanum Lighting District, 1914, 1920 (Box 88, Folder 21)
      - Hockanum Sewer District, 1920 (Box 88, Folder 22)
      - Meadows Fire District, 1921-1929, undated (Box 88, Folder 23)
      - Payroll (Box 88, Folder 24)
        - Engineering Dept.; Fire Dept.; Park Dept., 1930-1931 (Box 88, Folder 24)
        - Main St Improvement; New Cemetery; Wells Hall, 1930-1932 (Box 88, Folder 25)
        - Street Dept., 1930-1932 (Box 88, Folder 26)
        - Water Dept., 1930-1932 (Box 88, Folder 27)
      - Planting plan for lands owned by the East Hartford Fire District, Connecticut, 1906 April (Box 88, Folder 28)
      - Public Utilities Commission, Reports to the, 1922-1924 (Box 88, Folder 29)
      - Relief, Board of, 1918-1928 (Box 88, Folder 30)
      - Salaries, Water Dept., 1923-1925 (Box 88, Folder 31)
      - Seal, Town, 1930 (Box 88, Folder 32)
      - Sewers: Chapman St., 1916-1917, undated (Box 88, Folder 33)
      - State highway commissioner, 1913-1928 (Box 88, Folder 34)
      - Streets (Box 88, Folder 35)
        - Burnside Avenue, 1911-1915 (Box 88, Folder 35)
        - Burnside Avenue, Minutes of hearing before Board of Commissioners concerning widening, 1911 September 19, 1926 (Box 88, Folder 36)
        - Bidwell Ave; Blinn St.; Central Ave.; Chapel St.; Church St.; Clark St.; Daniel St., 1911-1916 (Box 88, Folder 37)
        - Elm St.; Elmer St; Garvan St.; Hammer St., 1910-1921 (Box 88, Folder 38)
        - John and Howard Streets, Larrabee St.; Macadam St; Main St; Oak St; Olmsted St., 1905-1922, undated (Box 88, Folder 39)
      - Time record of delinquent tax forms, 1935-1936 (Box 88, Folder 40)
      - Water collections, 1930 (Box 88, Folder 41)
      - Water connections, 1930-1931 (Box 88, Folder 42-45)
      - Water extension guarantees due, 1928-1931 (Box 88, Folder 46)
      - Water extensions, 1900-1920, undated (Box 88, Folder 47)
      - Water Works report, 1905-1929, undated (Box 88, Folder 48)
    - Annual and special meeting minutes, 1890-1929 (Box 92)
      - 1890 March 14 - 1907 August 7, 1 volume (Box 92)
      - 1908 June 9 - 1929 June 21, 1 volume (Box 92)
    - Assessment cards
      - D-Z, undated (Box 89)
      - circa 1924-1934 (Box 90)
        Includes tax cards.
    - Board of Commissioners minutes, 1904-1914, 1924-1929
      - 1904 March 1 - 1911 March 7, 1 volume (Box 91)
      - 1911 March 28 - 1914 December 15, 1 volume (Box 91)
      - 1924 January 8 - 1929 June 18, 1 volume (Box 91)
        Includes minutes of the Village Improvement Society annual minutes, 1925-1929.
      - 1929 July 2 - October 1 (Box 91)
        Includes Town Council minutes, October 8, 1929; and Village Improvement Society minutes, 1935.
    - Cash book, 1913-1921; 1 volume (Box 92)
    - Check stub book, 1929; 1 volume (Box 92)
    - Index, circa 1901-1929; 1 volume (Box 92)
    - Journal, 1928-1929 (Box 92)
    - Orders, Abstracts of, 1900-1932
      - 1900-1914, 1 volume (Box Item 93)
      - 1914-1921, 1 volume (Box Item 94)
      - 1922-1928, 1 volume (Box Item 95)
      - 1929-1930, 1 volume (Box Item 96)
      - Water account, 1922-1932; 1 volume (Box Item 97)
    - Tax abstracts, 1926-1928
      - 1926 (Box Item 98)
      - 1927 (Box Item 99)
      - 1928 (Box Item 100)
    - Tax lists, 1896-1927, undated
      - 1896, 1892, 1899, 1900, 1902, 1905, 1908, 1909. 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915, 1916, 13 volumes (Box 101)
      - 1917, 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1925, 1927, undated, 7 volumes, 2 notebooks (Box 102)
    - Water Dept. inspectors reports (Box 103)
      - 1914, 1 volume (Box 103)
      - 1922, 2 volumes (Box 103)
    - Water Dept. water rents cashbooks (Box 103)
      - 1911-1919, 1 volume (Box 103)
      - 1925-1929, 1 volume (Box 103)
  - Hockanum Lighting District
    - Bank book and statements: East Hartford Trust Company, 1916-1929 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Collector oath and resignation, 1928-1929 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Ledger book, 1916-1929 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Meeting notices, 1926-1929 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Minute book, 1916-1929 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Orders and payments, 1929 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Reports, 1928-1929, undated (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Hockanum Sewer District (Box 104)
    - Meeting notices, minutes, reports, 1915-1929 (Box 104, Folder 8-9)
  - Meadow Fire District (Box 104)
    - Agreement with East Hartford Fire District, 1921 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Bank papers, 1926-1928 (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - City Bank and Trust Company, 1926-1928 (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - East Hartford Trust Company, 1925-1928 (Box 104, Folder 12)
      - East Hartford Trust Company: cancelled checks, 1929 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Building permit applications, 1925-1926, undated (Box 104, Folder 14-15)
    - Correspondence, 1921-1928 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Election papers, 1922-1927 (Box 104, Folder 17)
      Includes lists of electors, 1922, 1926-1927; election results, 1923; ballot box key.
    - Financial papers, 1922-1928, undated (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Licenses and permits, 1922-1929 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Meeting notices and minutes, 1922-1928 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Officials, Lists of, 1924, 1927, undated (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Orders, 1919-1922, 1927-1929 (Box 104, Folder 22-24)
    - Petitions, 1923, 1926-1929, undated (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Receipts, 1922-1929, undated (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Sewer: Holland and Emily Streets, 1925-1928, undated (Box 104, Folder 27)
    - Taxes, 1919-1926 (Box 104, Folder 28)
    - Taxes received, 1928-1929 (Box 104, Folder 29)
    - Treasurer reports, 1922, 1925-1926 (Box 104, Folder 30)
  - Silver Lane Fire and Lighting District (Box 104)
    - Taxes received, 1926-1929 (Box 104, Folder 31)